A Finding Aid to the Rosamund Felsen Gallery Records, 1949-2014, bulk 1978-2014, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
Rosamund Felsen Gallery records
1949-2014
bulk 1978-2014
Archives of American Art
Rosamund Felsen Gallery
AAA.rosafelg
Archival Resource Key
28.9 Linear feet
The Rosamund Felsen Gallery records measure 28.9 linear feet and date from 1949 to 2014, with the bulk of the records dating from 1978 to 2014. The records shed light on the gallery's operations primarily through administrative records, artist files, exhibition and event files, financial records, born digital material, photographs, and slides.
Biographical / Historical
The Rosamund Felsen Gallery was established in 1978 in Los Angeles, California by Rosamund Felsen. The gallery closed its physical location in 2016 after nearly four decades as a widely influential contemporary art gallery.
In 1960, Rosamund Felsen began her art career working as an assistant registrar for the Pasadena Art Museum, and eventually became curator of prints. Felsen also worked at Gemini GEL: Graphics Editions Limited alongside her second husband, Gemini co-founder Sidney Felsen. From these positions, Felsen became friendly with both established and younger artists, learned to mount exhibitions, and participated in art-related operations. In 1977, Timothea Stewart asked Felsen if she would like to work at her new gallery. After two exhibitions, Felsen took over the Timothea Stewart Gallery and started her own.
Rosamund Felsen gallery exhibited artists working in various mediums, including video and sound, and frequently showed live performance art. Early artists exhibited at the gallery included Richard Jackson, Keith Sonnier, Maria Nordman, Chris Burden, and William Wegman. Felsen gallery opened Robert Rauschenberg's In + Out City Limits: Los Angeles (1981) on New Year's Eve; and added artists Jeffrey Vallance, Mike Kelley, Lari Pittman, and Erika Rothenberg to its roster by the end of the 1980s. Felsen brought on a list of new artists in the 1990s, including Paul McCarthy, Renee Petropoulos, Tim Ebner, Meg Cranston, Steven Hull, and Nancy Jackson. The gallery continued to show solo and group exhibitions of its artists, and featured a run of smaller artist-curated exhibitions of local and international artists. The Project Wall exhibitions included artist/curators Andrea Bowers and Steven Hull and showed European artists Erwin Wurm and Nils Norman. By 2004, Felsen's artists were all living in Los Angeles except for two, video artists Judith Barry and Joan Jonas.
In 1990, the gallery moved from Los Angeles to West Hollywood on Santa Monica Boulevard. Four years later, Felsen Gallery moved to a location in the Bergamot Station Arts Center, where it remained until 2015. After Bergamot, the gallery moved to the Arts District in Los Angeles. Rosamund Felsen Gallery closed its physical location in 2016, but continued representing a number of artists online.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged as four series.
Series 1: Administrative Records, 1968-2013 (2 linear feet; Box 1-2, OV 30-33)
Series 2: Artist Files, 1949-2013, bulk 1978-2006 (19.7 linear feet; Box 22-25, OV 34)
Series 3: Exhibition and Event Files, 1979-2014 (3.7 linear feet; Box 22-25, OV 34-36)
Series 4: Financial Records, 1978-2014 (3.5 linear feet; Box 25-29)
Scope and Contents
The Rosamund Felsen Gallery records measure 28.9 linear feet and date from 1949 to 2014, with the bulk of the records dating from 1978 to 2014. The records shed light on the gallery's operations primarily through administrative records, artist files, exhibition and event files, financial records, born digital material, photographs, and slides.
Administrative records consist of advertising files, property records, a gallery notebook, gallery digital files, and more. Also included in this series are several folders comprised of Rosamund Felsen's personal and professional papers and photographs. Artist files consist of resumes, slides and photographs of artists and their work, printed mnaterial, some sales and consignment records, and correspondence. Artists represented in the collection include Richard Jackson, Kaz Oshiro, Tim Ebner, John Boskovich, Jeff Gambill, Jeffrey Vallance, Mitchell Syrop, Mac James, Marnie Weber, Keith Sklar, Leland Rice, Erika Rothenberg, Peter Lodato, Paul McCarthy, Jim Shaw, Al Ruppersberg, Ilya Kabakov, Lari Pittman, Cisco Jiménez, Chris Burden, Mike Kelley, and Heidi Kidon.
Exhibition and event files relate to Rosamund Felsen Gallery exhibitions and performances as well as a number of art fairs and exhibitions held at other galleries and museum spaces. The files contain consignment and sales records, check lists, born digital material, photographs and slides, installation directions, printed material, and more. Financial records contain primarily sales records, invoices, some correspondence, and receipts.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research. Access to original papers requires an appointment and is limited to the Archives' Washington, D.C. Research Center. Researchers interested in accessing born-digital records or audiovisual recordings in this collection must use access copies. Contact References Services for more information.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The collection was donated in several installments from 2014 to 2016 by the Rosamund Felsen Gallery via Rosamund Felsen, gallery founder and owner. Rosamund Felsen Letters and Postcards were donated in 2016 by Rosamund Felsen.
Related Materials
Also found in the Archives of American Art is an oral history interview with Rosamund Felsen conducted by Anne Ayres, October 11, 2004.
Scrapbooks; Art galleries, Commercial -- California; Women art dealers; Acerol, Ali; Ackerman, Robert E.; Beach, Alicia; Bengston, Billy Al; Boskovich, John; Cranston, Meg; Dowell, Roy; Gambrill, Jeff; Kabakov, Ilʹia︠ ︡Iosifovich, 1933-; Kidon, Heidi; Jackson, Richard; Lodato, Peter; McCarthy, Paul; Oshiro, Kaz, 1967-; Pittman, Lari, 1952-; Rauschenberg, Robert, 1925-2008; Rothenberg, Erika; Ruppersberg, Allen, 1944-; Shaw, Jim, 1952-; Smith, Alexis, 1949-; Sonnier, Keith, 1941-2020; Syrop, Mitchell, 1953-; Vallance, Jeffrey; Weber, Marnie; Kelley, Mike, 1954-2012; Burden, Chris, 1946-; Jiménez, Cisco, 1969-; Felsen, Rosamund, 1934-
- Administrative Records, 1968-2013; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 2 Linear feet Box 1-2, OV 30-33
  Scope and Contents
  Administrative records consists of the drafts, price lists, invoices, and correspondence relating to the gallery's advertising in various art publications; appraisal records; papers relating to the gallery's location at Bergamot Station Art Center in Santa Monica; a gallery notebook; inventories of photographs taken by Douglas M. Parker Studio of artwork; born digital material, webpage printouts, and printed material from the internet site, Striking Distance; and gallery press releases.
  Also included in this series are some of gallery founder Rosamund Felsen's personal and professional papers. Included are photographs and resumes; printed material and correspondence from Felsen's lectures, panel appearances, and interviews; and sixteen letters and two postcards, all but three of which are from Jasper Johns. The others are from Ellsworth Kelly, Al Ruppersberg, and Bob P.
  - Advertising, General, 1993, 2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Association of Museums, Facility Reports, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Appraisals, 1990-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
  - Artforum, 1988-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Art in America, 1978, 1990-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Art issues, 1988-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Artweek, 1978-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Authenticity, Letters of, 1998-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - A, Miscellaneous, 1979, 1990-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Bergamot Station Art Center, 1994-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - B, Miscellaneous, 1990-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Contracts, Artist Commission, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - C-F, Miscellaneous, 1990-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 14-16)
  - Felsen, Rosamund, Biographical Material, 2000-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Felsen, Rosamund, Letters and Postcards, 1968-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Felsen, Rosamund, Photographs, 1980-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Felsen, Rosamund, Pasadena Art Museum Scrapbook (1 of 4), 1965-1967; Archival Resource Key (Oversize 30)
  - Felsen, Rosamund, Pasadena Art Museum Scrapbook (2 of 4), 1965-1967; Archival Resource Key (Oversize 31)
  - Felsen, Rosamund, Pasadena Art Museum Scrapbook (3 of 4), 1965-1967; Archival Resource Key (Oversize 32)
  - Felsen, Rosamund, Pasadena Art Museum Scrapbook (4 of 4), 1965-1967; Archival Resource Key (Oversize 33)
  - Frieze, 1992-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Gallery Guide, 1991-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - G-K, Miscellaneous, 1990-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 22-24)
  - L. A. Times, 1979-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - L. A. Weekly, 1979-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Lectures, Panels, and Interviews, 1984-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - L-P, Miscellaneous, 1991-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 28-29)
  - Notebook, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Parkett, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Photography, Inventory, 1988-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Photography, Inventory, 1988-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 1-3)
  - Press Releases, Felsen Gallery, 1991-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Printed Material, Articles and Clippings, 1982-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Printed Material, Los Angeles Artists Calendar, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - The Pollock-Krasner Foundation, 1989-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - R, Miscellaneous, 1992-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Staff, 1993-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - S, Miscellaneous, 1991-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Striking Distance, 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key; Includes two CDs. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Travel, 1991-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - T-Z, Miscellaneous, 1989-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Web Files, Felsen Gallery, undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 Electronic discs (CD) (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Artist Files, 1949-2013; bulk 1978-2006; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 19.7 Linear feet Box 2-22, OV 34
  Files might include artist resumes; born digital material, slides, transparencies, and photographs of artists, artwork, and installations; correspondence ranging from business affairs to more personal matters; writings and drafts of artist statements, catalogs, and essays; exhibition catalogs and announcements; newspaper and magazine articles and appearances; and some exhibition material such as check lists, price lists, and sales records. Some files also include sketches and photocopies of drawings. Artists with more extensive representation in this series include Patrick Hogan, Erika Rothenberg, Mike Kelly, Lari Pittman, Jim Shaw, Chris Burden, Tim Ebner, Marnie Weber, and Ilya Kabakov.
  Included in Patrick Hogan's files are photographs taken throughout his life, at events held in his honor, his family and residence, and of his many exhibitions and paintings. Of particular note are images of the artist's studio, including depictions of the mechanism that assisted Hogan—born with a form of spinal atrophy—to complete his paintings.
  - Acerol, Ali, 1994-2010; Archival Resource Key; Includes two CDs. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Acerol, Ali, Slides and Transparencies, 1996-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Ackerman, Robert, 1983-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Ackerman, Robert, Slides, Photographs, and Transparencies, 1981-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Andrews, Oliver, 1977-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Beach, Alicia, 2000-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Beach, Alicia, Slides and Transparencies, 2000-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Bengston, Billy Al, 1984-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Bengston, Billy Al, Slides and Transparencies, 1961-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 3-4)
  - Boskovich, John, 1987-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Boskovich, John, Exhibitions at Felsen Gallery, 1988-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Boskovich, John, Printed Material, 1988-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Boskovich, John, Slides, Photographs, and Transparencies, 1987-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 8-10)
  - Brown, Greg, 1983-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Burden, Chris, 1978-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 12-13)
  - Burden, Chris, Exhibitions at Felsen Gallery, 1979, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Burden, Chris, Printed Material, 1975-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 15-16)
  - Burden, Chris, Slides, Photographs, and Transparencies, 1979-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Burden, Chris, Slides, Photographs, and Transparencies, 1979-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Burkhart, Dan, 1978-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Bush, Stephen, 1997-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 3-4)
  - Bush, Stephen, Printed Material, 1994-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 5-6)
  - Cooper, Laura, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Cooper, Ron, 1978-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Cooper, Ron, Exhibitions at Felsen Gallery, 1979-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Cooper, Ron, Slides and Photographs, 1970s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 10-11)
  - Cranston, Meg, 1995-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Cranston, Meg, Exhibitions at Felsen Gallery, 1996-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Cranston, Meg, Printed Material, 1991-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 14-15)
  - Cranston, Meg, Slides and Photographs, 1995-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - de Cointet, Guy, Preparatory Drawings, circa 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Den Hartog, Jacci, 1990s-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Dill, Guy, 1978-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Dill, Guy, Sketches, 1978, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Dill, Guy, Printed Material, 1972-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Dill, Guy, Slides and Photographs, 1977-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Dowell, Roy, 1986-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Dowell, Roy, Printed Material, 1986-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 5-6)
  - Dowell, Roy, Slides and Photographs, 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 7-12)
  - Ebner, Tim, Transparencies, 1996-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 13-16)
  - Ebner, Tim, Slides, 1979-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 1-8)
  - Ellis, Stephen, 1991-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Gambil, Jeff, 1988-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Gambil, Jeff, Exhibitions at Felsen Gallery, 1991-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Gambil, Jeff, Printed Material, 1988-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Gambil, Jeff, Slides, Photographs, and Transparencies, 1984-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 13-14)
  - Hayward, James, 1985-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Hogan, Patrick, 1976-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Hogan, Patrick, Drawing from Childhood, circa 1951; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Hogan, Patrick, Printed Material, 1965-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Hogan, Patrick, Photographs and Transparencies, 1949-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 1-3)
  - Huebler, Darcy, 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Hull, Steven, "Rainy Day Doodles", undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 computer_disc_3.5 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Hull, Steven, Slides and Transparencies, 1990s-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 6-7)
  - Hurd, Steve, Slides and Transparencies, 2004-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Jackson, Nancy, Slides and Transparencies, 1998-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 9-10)
  - Jackson, Richard, 1978-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Jackson, Richard, Exhibitions at Felsen Gallery, 1980-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Jackson, Richard, Printed Material, 1978-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Jackson, Richard, Photographs and Slides, 1978-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Jackson, Richard, Photographs and Slides, 1978-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - James, Mac, 1984, 1996-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - James, Mac, Slides, Transparencies and Images, 1998-2004; Archival Resource Key; Includes one CD. (Box 8, Folder 2-4)
  - Jiminez, Cisco, 1997-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Jiminez, Cisco, Slides and Photographs, 1997-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 6-7)
  - Jonas, Joan, "Electric Wires", 2006 January 23; Archival Resource Key; 2 Videodiscs (DVD) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Jonas, Joan, "Mirror Improv", 2006 January 23; Archival Resource Key; 2 Videodiscs (DVD) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Jonas, Joan, "Melancholia", 2006 January 25; Archival Resource Key; 2 Videodiscs (DVD) (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Jonas, Joan, "The Shape, The Scent, The Feel of Things", 2006 January 25; Archival Resource Key; 2 Videodiscs (DVD) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Jonas, Joan, "Wolf Lights", 2006 January 25; Archival Resource Key; 2 Videodiscs (DVD) (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Jonas, Joan, Slides and Transparencies, 1990s-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Kabakov, Ilya, 1990s-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 14-17)
  - Kabakov, Ilya, Printed Material, 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Kabakov, Ilya, Slides, Photographs, and Transparencies, 1989-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Kahn, Steve, 1979-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Kaino, Glenn, 1998-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Kaino, Glenn, Printed Material, 1993-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 5-6)
  - Kelley, Mike, 1986-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 7-10)
  - Kelley, Mike, Exhibitions, 1983-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 11-13)
  - Kelley, Mike, Interview with John Miller, 1991 March 21; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Kelley, Mike, Project Proposal, 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Kelley, Mike, Texts and Writings, 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Kelley, Mike, Printed Material, 1978-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Kelley, Mike, Printed Material, 1978-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
  - Kelley, Mike, Transparencies, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Kelly, Mary, 1993-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Kelly, Mary, Exhibitions at Felsen Gallery, 2002-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Kelly, Mary, Printed Material, 2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Kelly, Mary, Slides and Transparencies, 1980s-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Kidon, Heidi, 1999-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Kidon, Heidi, Slides and Transparencies, 1990s-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 9-12)
  - Knechtel, Tom, 1992-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Lawson, Thomas, 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Lightbody, Joyce, 1987-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Lodato, Peter, 1978-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Lodato, Peter, Slides, Photographs, and Transparencies, 1973-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 17-18)
  - Lowe, Jean, "Woman in Colorful Room", undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 Electronic discs (CD) (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Lowe, Jean, Slides and Transparencies, 1990s-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 1-3)
  - MacConnel, Kim, Slides, Photographs, and Transparencies, 1970s-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 4-7)
  - McCarthy, Paul, 1991-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - McCarthy, Paul, Printed Material, 1980-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 9-12)
  - McCarthy, Paul, Slides and Photographs, 1970s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 1-5)
  - McCarty, Kevin, 2005-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Miller, John, 1984-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Miller, John, Slides, 1983-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Mudford, Grant, "Planet Architecture", 1999; Archival Resource Key; 1 Electronic discs (CD) (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Mudford, Grant, "8X10 Files", undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 Electronic discs (CD) (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Mudford, Grant, Slides, 1970s-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 11-12)
  - Newkirk, Kori, 1998-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Newkirk, Kori, Printed Material, 1990s-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 14-15)
  - Newkirk, Kori, Slides and Transparencies, 1990-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 16-17)
  - Nordman, Maria, 1978-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
  - Nordman, Maria, Photographs of Artwork from Felsen Exhibition, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - O'Neill, Pat, 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Orser, Julie, 2005; Archival Resource Key; Includes two DVDs. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Oshiro, Kaz, 2002-2010; Archival Resource Key; Includes one CD. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Oshiro, Kaz, Exhibitions, 2005-2009; Archival Resource Key; Includes four CDs. (Box 13, Folder 7-8)
  - Oshiro, Kaz, Printed Material, 2004-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 9-10)
  - Oshiro, Kaz, Slides, Photographs, and Transparencies, 1999-2006; Archival Resource Key; Includes one CD. (Box 13, Folder 11-12)
  - Owens, Laura, 1994-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Owens, Laura, Slides and Transparencies, 1994-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Pally, Marc, Slides, 1987-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Peers, M. A., Slides and photographs, 1993-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Peipon, Corrina, 2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Petropoulos, Renee, "Gas Station Mini Marts: Station 3", undated; Archival Resource Key; 4 Electronic discs (DVD) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Petropoulos, Renee, Slides, Photographs, and Transparencies, 1980s-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 2-7)
  - Pettibon, Raymond, 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Pittman, Lari, 1983-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 9-10)
  - Pittman, Lari, Exhibitions at Felsen Gallery, 1983-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Pittman, Lari, Printed Material, 1983-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 12-14)
  - Pittman, Lari, Photographs, 1983-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Pittman, Slides, Photographs, and Transparencies, 1978-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 1-7)
  - Preston, Ann, Slides, 1987-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 8)